<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>Meow@B612</title>
  
  <subtitle>Joy of the New</subtitle>
  <link href="http://meowb612.xyz/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  
  <link href="http://meowb612.xyz/"/>
  <updated>2021-10-31T13:26:27.086Z</updated>
  <id>http://meowb612.xyz/</id>
  
  <author>
    <name>Matilda Y</name>
    
  </author>
  
  <generator uri="https://hexo.io/">Hexo</generator>
  
  <entry>
    <title>A Lime Tree</title>
    <link href="http://meowb612.xyz/2020/07/01/lime-tree/"/>
    <id>http://meowb612.xyz/2020/07/01/lime-tree/</id>
    <published>2020-07-01T13:13:44.000Z</published>
    <updated>2021-10-31T13:26:27.086Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="/images/2019_lime.jpg" alt="I drew a lime tree, and wrote her a poem." width="600"/>1 July, 2020<p>I had almost nothing back then<br>Neither blossoms nor fruits<br>My leaves were dim and my branches bare<br>Then you took me home, and we had one another.</p><p>I was happy and comfortable<br>Sitting in the nutritious, warm soil<br>No mores pests intruding my lovely siestas<br>There’s nothing else I’d ask for.</p><p>But soon I started to feel <br>A bit lethargic, fatigued<br>As if part of my youth was drained.</p><p>Still, I gave all I have<br>To permeate your house with aroma<br>And to grow the little green ones <br>Just to win your angel-like laughters<br>and delightful eyes. <br>Do you know that I love you so?</p><p>Time gone by, and there came a day<br>we had a new home.<br>I was left in the balcony, the sky was bright<br>And my body blazed with refreshed vitality.<br>I realised by then, that all I had truly needed<br>was sunshine. Eternal sunshine.</p><p>Polished, soft green leavesstart to crown my head<br>They gently swayed in the wind.<br>I knew that you were happy for me<br>And so was I, happy for you.<br>Because</p><p>I see you<br>kissed her in the moonlight,<br>I see you<br>stunned at the mesmerising sunset<br>I see you<br>lost yourself with the piano<br>your silhouette bathed in the warm, amber light.</p><p>Do you know that I love you so?<br>I think you do.</p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;img src=&quot;/images/2019_lime.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;I drew a lime tree, and wrote her a poem.&quot; width=&quot;600&quot;/&gt;
1 July, 2020

&lt;p&gt;I had almost nothing back th</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="stardust" scheme="http://meowb612.xyz/categories/stardust/"/>
    
    
    <category term="poems" scheme="http://meowb612.xyz/tags/poems/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Neruda, I</title>
    <link href="http://meowb612.xyz/2020/03/21/neruda/"/>
    <id>http://meowb612.xyz/2020/03/21/neruda/</id>
    <published>2020-03-21T13:28:50.000Z</published>
    <updated>2021-10-31T13:47:45.693Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>20 March, 2020<br><small><em>This poem was written as my tribute to Neruda’s Poem: Tonight I Can Write the Saddest Lines.</em></small><br><br><br></p><p>Tonight I can write the saddest lines.<br>Inside my mind I shrieked until I turned mute,<br>silence befallen and the eternal song died.</p><p>All the tiny beautiful things<br>that sewed us together,<br>now winding into a long thin strand<br>Entangling my lungs, robbing me of my life.<br>Your disappearance leaves me in a continuous void of emotionlessness.</p><p>Tonight I can write the saddest lines.</p><p>Your smell had been strolling at the edge of my mind,<br>driving me mad, mad at the fact now<br>even my olfaction is under your tyrannous reign — Also my vision,<br>constantly being invaded by your loving, soft eyes. Also my hands and body,<br>desperately seeking those counterparts of mine. Also my ears,<br>echoing Chopin’s ballades that you played for me,<br>thus away I pined.</p><p>Tonight I can write the saddest lines;<br>no, I couldn’t. For as long I could write, I was still alive.<br>I could still write when thinking of your being by my side.<br>Your eyes would wet as I read to you my poem then you would hug me tight.<br>As this fog of happy illusions gradually lifted, from this world was I effaced.</p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;20 March, 2020&lt;br&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;This poem was written as my tribute to Neruda’s Poem: Tonight I Can Write the Saddest Lines.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;br</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="stardust" scheme="http://meowb612.xyz/categories/stardust/"/>
    
    
    <category term="poems" scheme="http://meowb612.xyz/tags/poems/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
</feed>
